Hello friends, today we are going to talk
about this policy, press it like this, guaranteed income for tomorrow, if
you have any doubt about this policy, Baba
Financial Year 10 of Fixed Deposit FD, okay, then
which one should you take, which one will
work for you, then for that I gave you some
idea, I will
try to clear some of your confusion,
subscribe and
[music]
subscribe here, so that
you can press any one,
click here like this, it flopped, earlier I
tortured
Bluetooth, there are
benefits, abe, it is
not working, there was a comment,
then if you have doubts, continue further,
solution, put this lakh rupees here,
how much do you have to invest here,
you need 1 lakh rupees here, and
for this you should do a 10 year
Uttam Nagar policy, click here, the
power station comes, okay, click on this here, then
here you will get the ID,
how much money are you getting, in which
definitely take it completely, it will come, from how many
years to how many pack abs, I will give you Amla
Lu  If you have made it here then you can see that
if you have made an Android agreement in the policy then
what benefit are you getting, if
you have purchased the policy and
see in it, it is being
told that if you
quit smoking, okay and in this,
if you have used the option benefit of Rs 1 lakh
and you have chosen guaranteed income for 15 years, then
how much money are you getting in it, then you are
getting a return of Rs 750 in this policy, if you are watching this video for the first
time, then in this policy I have told
you that you can get computer
labs,
subscribe,
if you
must
subscribe to this video then you are getting a guaranteed income of Rs 1 lakh one lakh,
240 rupees per
year, you are getting it,
if you have seen it then
after subscribing you will
get it, that is
scooter driving, that is why
I tell you that
first you
subscribe here, then subscribe here, then
you have the assurance
that you will get this money with 10 computer
documents, okay  Okay, you have
added this much here, in this
you will get like, this is 1 lakh
subscribe, you
can subscribe, okay,
but you are
getting it, okay, so the subscription is
posted in the subscription,
that is fine, but you will put it in this mode,
okay, Vishal, you have
posted this among the people, in the first year you are
not getting any interest, in the
second year you will put this on one lakh, if
you have put it before that then you will
get its base, secondly, if you put it on one then it will
come in your deposit, so
like and
subscribe,
appoint
subscribe, if
you are
not getting the subscription then
subscribe, subscribe, subscribe, subscribe, do subscribe from
here, okay, this is for life,
you only need 15, but if
I
subscribe, then if you have
subscribed, then how much money you were getting here,
then you are getting a
lot on the score, then
you must subscribe to the
subscribe button here, that is,
school, you have
subscribed to the company,
but the story here is one and a half that
your problem is that this is absolutely fine,
in this you should subscribe to this normal
subscribe
So how much money is the
subscription
company
getting from subscribing? If
you subscribe here,
you will be taxed on it,
but
if your
subscription is very less, then okay, then here you subscribe, then
subscribe to the gas,
if you
subscribe,
like and subscribe,
okay, you are getting it, after that what
promise do they give that they will take 22% of the amount of love, that is, lakhs and lakhs,
so
subscribe, subscribe,
but
definitely subscribe, subscribe, if you subscribe, then
here they are giving you returns,
how many numbers are there in between, if you do love,
your polish will be done, you will have to pay the charges,
you will
not have to pay that charge, charge, charge, charge, okay, so this is with you,
but
how much money do
you get from subscribing? You
cannot subscribe to the channel appointed here, but you
can take this subscription for your family,
okay, so in this you get
one and a half benefits from the lift company on debt, Avni has
taken it from the first year,
dip benefit of yours in the first year, this against packing of 1
lakh has been put in, of one lakh  If you have
applied in the second year then you are lucky, after 10 years
your Samson will be auspicious, there is
some ups and downs in this, you have doctored,
this interest here is okay, so in this your SMS will be more than
20-25 thousand
rupees here, you don't need to do anything because you have
already done this interview here, you
can add it here, okay, not on the submission date, from the
previous date, only after that the SIM will be
charged with GST, this is the
first option with financial income and this
is the income distributed by river police
officer,
so what do you think, if you want to buy from this point, then
you like the idea,
you want to buy from this point,
mix it on the policy now, but you do
not want interest, you
want a crorepati war, then if you want to buy pregnancy, then
subscribe to it,
but if you
subscribe,
but now
if you
want to buy skin, then you have posted in the comment box, so if you have liked
our channel till now, then
you can press the subscribe button,
in the coming videos, more new
investment classes have come, very
good insurance companies have just been launched,
their competition note is going on  Friend, right now
he should bring all those problems on time, so
keep making such videos, that's all for today, thank you.